{
  "Title": "Round 5: Covers! Name the song, original artist and cover artist. 1 point for each.",
  "Questions": [
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Kate Bush - Running up that hill (covered by Placebo)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/0uYVJ8z5kgMayMNPJA6Cz9?si=8cfcb083c1b642e5",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "The Cure - Just like heaven (covered by Katie Melua)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/2tHj8vYlXs8bpqeaHHqUAZ?si=4b3346e0fb9f45a2",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Jimmy Hendrix - All along the watchtower (covered by U2)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/3jbgBiIM5vMUr2RcLNYghI?si=c272513b1c404936",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Talk Talk - It's my life (covered by No Doubt)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/1OutzYv6YiN93lrT3pJsWR?si=05123b1612a54956",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Dolly Parton - I will always love you (covered by Whitney Houston)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/4eHbdreAnSOrDDsFfc4Fpm?si=e601c84742f24467",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Nirvana - Smells like teen spirit (covered by Tori Amos)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/1kWqRB6PHLM9QTfaXuHpIV?si=2ee95a6135784937",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Simon Garfunkel - Mrs. Robinson (covered by Lemonheads)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/1Hnv9uDIokwi4nkcVUyS0X?si=6406b01749334b47",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Police - I'll be missing you (covered by Puff Daddy)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/3QHONiXGMGU3z68mQInncF?si=ef829ca20e534353",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Backstreet Boys - As long as you love me (covered by The Kik)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/5wOWp3hllZdaeG29Czds3a?si=7d1bb483d9ae4a6a",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "",
      "Answer": "Eminem - Lose yourself (covered by Kasey Chambers)",
      "Tracks": [
        {
          "SpotifyUrl": "https://open.spotify.com/track/4v0Lu9dboiL2jeGvtvBiQT?si=5ac95bef3c734f0b",
          "Offset": 0,
          "Duration": 5000
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
